He loved her from afar. It wasn't far enough.
Mr. Wrong is a comedy, romance film directed by Nick Castle.
A single and lonely woman finds the seemingly perfect man to date, but soon regrets it when his deranged and possessive
other personality emerges and worst still, she cannot convince anyone else of his Jekyll/Hyde true nature.
Martha Alston, played by Ellen DeGeneres.
Whitman Crawford, played by Bill Pullman.
Inga Gunther, played by Joan Cusack.
Jack Tramonte, played by Dean Stockwell.
Mrs. Crawford, played by Joan Plowright.
Walter, played by John Livingston.
Wrong is a 1996 American romantic black comedy film starring Ellen DeGeneres in her film debut
and Bill Pullman, and produced by Touchstone Pictures and Mandeville Films.
It was released on February 16, 1996, by Buena Vista Pictures Distribution.
The film's story follows the misadventures of a woman who
realizes her fiancé is a mentally disturbed criminal.
Wrong was a critical failure and box office bomb, being lambasted by critics.
DeGeneres used to mention the film occasionally on her talk
show, poking fun at the disastrous reception.
As of 2025, it remains her first and only film as
lead actress in a live-action film.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.